all right welcome to I am gonna say fix
our world Friday because I think our
world could really use fixing right now
yeah and it's it's gone a little chaotic
in the last two weeks for sure mmm
welcome to fix our roll Friday let's fix
it we got an hour guys wait 30 minutes
to spare
yeah what was our agenda today I haven't
we don't have an agenda we have I open
the agenda we didn't even put anything
on there two weeks ago and so it's I
think it's just like updating what it is
we're doing with this time period and
tomorrow as well as um update you won't
what I'm in the process of doing and if
you guys want to update that as well
you're in the process of doing either
four together check and of course your
individual projects as well and then
chat about the ridiculousness of the
world and what's what's going on
Oh more or less leaving stuff up to our
politicians and how different it is
depending on who is in charge and how
how open they are to the truth how much
dirt Lissie died over notes may vary yes
your results may vary so I sent out the
doodle poll or to see if we can get
other projects to meet there was only
two people who filled it out and
tomorrow works for them for 9 a.m. I
believe it was so I say I invite them
right after and we have a 9 a.m. project
meeting or because that's I mean we
leave it much passed there was the only
one that was one person felt that was
the only time that worked for them they
have the person that was one of the
times it worked and it worked for all of
us of course it's the only meet there I
put out the message on Facebook saying
to change your account setting to all
notifications I don't know if anyone
actually did that but like Facebook just
it's the best we got and it's not it's
same with our government so the best we
got right now and they're in no way
adequate and it's like Facebook is the
best we have to get people to come and
yet it's no way adequate and then of
course everyone's also going through the
chaos of their lives and so it's I was
just gonna put a post and I did me on
the project
group just asking like how's your
project doing during the pandemic like
is it because I think for some people
it's completely falling by the wayside
and for other people it's been the fire
under there but to be like the world
needs these things and a combination
right everyone has to go through their
own mourning process and their own just
constant self regulation right on all
this stuff and so I think the best thing
you can do for projects is honor that
together and like just show up and even
if that is the case you're like I
haven't touched this in six months and I
want to do it now or hey the world
doesn't need sense making what we need
is about speed
I don't know right like like whatever it
is for the for the project person but I
will reach out to the two people who
have never spoken to where the only two
who filled out the doodle poll and then
also just for everyone else just saying
okay we keep the two people filled it
out here is the meeting we're having
bring yourself bring your projects we're
going to have a project meeting and part
of that will be discussing should we do
this weekly should we do a bi-weekly
what is it that we're doing and what
does that look like which we keep trying
to figure out for our projects but it
doesn't work so well and there's only
three of us we need more people with
more feedback and more diversity of
projects um and so that's what I've done
for together Tech I'm going live as of
tonight every day from 6:00 every night
from 6:00 to 6:40 it's like a 40-minute
live video hopefully to get the message
out that we need a tech cooperative we
need a solutions cooperative like here's
all the reasons it would have been great
to have it during the pandemic and it's
still not too late you keep learn at
home and to give people hope and really
just do it I'm here to do it's not
really together tech it won't be on
together text um I'll be online
Jubilees save the world by meandering
through life YouTube channel and just I
want to give people hope and I feel like
I have a bit of it or how I'm like okay
this isn't this isn't as devastating to
me as it is to other people and I think
a lot of people things I do you feel
that way they're like oh the rest of the
world kind of you get it right or
it's which is also weird because both
our governments are doing the best they
can our medical system is doing the best
they can and those are both two things
and I'm very critical of normally and
I'm still critical of them but at the
same time
they're doing the best they can with
what they've been given and so we can't
make a really expect any of our elected
officials to do better than they're
currently doing they're doing exactly
who they are right Justin Trudeau is
actually like Justin Trudeau Trump's
acting like Trump and we're getting what
we we elect in for better for worse but
none of them were elected to deal with a
pandemic right none of them were
actually elected to deal with what is
going on and they're in no way capable
they're elected to be charismatic
leaders of countries and you know I
don't like they don't have all the
information and they're doing the best
they can at the moment so anyway so I'm
gonna be going live I'm trying to do a
video Monday Wednesday and Friday but
that's proving to be difficult because
my kid now has kid messenger on YouTube
and so they're constantly sending
ordered gifts and video chatting with
each other and it's somehow only works
on the iPad and that's what I recorded
videos on and if I'm going live every
day at 6:00 I don't know if I also need
to do it three videos a week but that is
what I'm up to because I feel like I do
have more capacity in this than other
people to do more than what other people
are doing because this is my normal this
is I think I'm missing a trail that you
had said like turns out my lifestyle is
called quarantine turns out yeah really
yeah all these questions like how does
it change for you there's more people
around my building where I work from
home that's about it it's now acceptable
that I only go out you know to stop
first groceries every two weeks under
than that don't really the house at one
point yeah all right have you guys been
doing over the last week or two weeks
depending on when did I last see you
changed so much I went on an airport
yesterday that was a whole fun trying to
get mom made us face masks we're even
through getting Aurora to try to wear it
it was lots of fun I got an apocalypse
photo it's like matching face masks
in their underground parking that looks
a little more apocalyptic than it was if
no cherry blossoms right looks like an
underground bunker of his work yeah
exactly
it's a little more yeah I can update on
what I've been up to
yeah it hasn't changed much for me at
all because I was didn't have a job as
working from home so except now my wife
is here every day so that's testing our
marriage we'll see if that survives the
apocalypse we're doing great
she's working from home too and I
tracked my time on working on recent
score this week and I logged 17 hours
and 44 minutes which sounds horrible
that's only half you know I don't have a
regular paying job so what am I doing
with the other twenty hours although I
am spending time taking care of my mom
some and stuff so that's that's kind of
it has been taking more time than usual
but I am feeling good because I am
making progress on reason score and it
was really just deciding how to do it
and I I was taking a training course on
design I decided to wait till I get the
back end of the system more solid with a
couple other changes I want to make
before I worry about the front end so
yeah that's that's where I'm at I was
hoping by the end this week I'd have a
working prototype with the new back-end
but it's probably gonna be next week
before that happens and that's mostly
what I've been working on
well could you slash not levity one of
our Facebook users but soon agreement
murid some fun with my walk lips yeah
yeah it's just that now the rest of the
world is in agreement but I was there
when did that actually start I think
that's the only real area of contention
is how long has this apocalypse been
going on for maybe we should call it the
proto pocalypse before apocalypse I like
that what my friends posted it was like
this is your like baby apocalypse if you
if you auto-renew if you don't if you
oughta do it we just gonna order a new
for three billion years or something
like that it was you don't figure out
your stuff yeah it's a trial apocalypse
it is and it's so fast like this is a
time skill where you can watch the
numbers increase and still our
politicians and people are in denial I'm
like no but the economy will be packed
by Easter at the slow-motion that's even
worse yeah with math please yeah it's
like we don't need ventilators making
ventilators I can only imagine if we
were on a timescale of decades what
what's that one for
Oh climate change a bigger one right one
that actually costs a hundred percent of
human lives you know and all of
biodiversity but we do have this baby
apocalypse to try and people are at home
dealing with all of their emotional
stuff and their marriages and all all of
and people come out with awesome stuff
Kira posted a um a video of her and her
husband dealing with kind of what every
marriage is going through right now
being home together it was really
amazing I was like we share this
everywhere you made it glow you mean
they have a youtube video caught our
YouTube channel about laptop counseling
or something and like if the world needs
this like I know me my kid or stuck home
all the time and now like my dad's here
too I mean you just can't go out he's
like I'm just gonna go to the store no
but it's like he's an adult he gets to
make his own decisions his his life and
it's you know that but like no you'd
like I want to lock you down like my
daughter like more than my daughter's
lock down his she'd me say more or less
we were excited about going to the post
office today that's how she was a little
because I hate grocery shopping but I'm
like oh I gotta go grocery shopping and
the bank oh yeah I gotta go to the bank
I gotta it's like Georgia's be coming
yeah did actually go out to the park
with a group of friends but we all sat 6
feet away
I had a ruler yeah so that was that was
fun and we're doing a lot of video
chatting and stuff so trying to stay
sane he's gonna see the big picture of
us it was in Colombia or Mexico or some
guy had made like a ring that was six
feet around him and was wearing it
around down
no I did say that's a good idea that was
great doors I guess but that's - Mexican
tell the side wait for me wait twelve
feet tall
I was like did wear hoop skirts for a
long time and had to figure that stuff
out yeah that's kind of like a forced
three foot buffer around you so how do
we get more people to these meetings or
do we just what do we do with these
meetings like the doodle poll getting
people involved I think just having that
change a bit of how the video works on
Saturday I think that will help because
I think the videos get more interest
than anything else and so seeing like
faces change people talking about the
doodle poll I think that will help you
know starting to see some up there oh
our viewer has a cunning plan
no your cunning plan is want to come on
come on video if you want I don't know
you are because it just says Facebook
user okay that means you're in our group
you're in the project crazy game be
projects that is something that has
changed for me now that the schools are
canceled for five months I no longer
have to hold the weekend is sacred
because I get my kid 24/7 so having that
that time period open up that's one of
the reasons I was like I can go live
from 6 to 640 no problem and doing
something on Saturdays and Sundays works
for me now because again all week we
have up so it's not just about keeping
those two days off for my kid um which
is you know beneficial so if we did have
a weekly project meeting then just it
for me if that was the whole reason but
it wasn't that I could it's now changed
or oh there we go
they're building a site called board at
home so stable to join the game be space
yeah that's we don't we don't know who
you are but yay
I can go check on the Facebook page but
right now that's not not happening so
Charlie when your internet has been slow
for us yeah there was actually a message
on stream yard before I went live that
was like YouTube Dudek Ovid 19
everyone's at home things are slow he's
like firstworldproblems hard internet
slowed down because everyone's streaming
videos I actually kind of think that is
accurate then two weeks then what we
will be dying for lack of 18 so I like
there's memes going around and I get it
that it's like like your grandparents
generation went to war all you're doing
is like happiness sit at home watch
Netflix like stay home but I think that
minimizes this what this actually is and
I mean like you're expected to do that
and yet we've minimized it and it's like
the emotional toll that's going to take
the relational ship told what that's
gonna take isn't nothing and for some to
some degree it's easier to go to war
it's easier to have a thing you're going
to that is a like you know what what's
expected of you and you know that you're
there until it's it's it's called off
this is like one it's like two weeks
that we know is gonna be extended and
extended and extended and it's minimized
we're like you're not seen of as a hero
right it's like as someone who's been
inside for six years more or less and
it's not like a hero
but it's you have to deal with the
emotional part and no one's gonna give
you credence for that and and no one's
going to like that you figure out
something to do from that space that our
relationships and our me our purpose in
life are to help one another or to
figure out a problem or whatever your
purpose is are huge and yet our entire
society is designed around how do you
make a living and how do you make that
have your your sense of self comes from
that and a lot of people are going to
realize that their job is not only not
essential like it's true
not essential their company can run
without their job the world can run
without their company and that's gonna
have a huge toll on people but at the
same time they are still worthy like
your worth was actually not tied to your
profession it was tied to you being a
human being but that also puts you on
par with everyone else and it's hard
when you're you know I was this AI was a
doctor no no doctors are still actually
you're the ones I saw have a really
didn't mean that was talking about like
that so this kind of pokes a hole in the
whole like if we get people ubi they
won't do anything no people are being
forced to stay at home and they're
stir-crazy they want to go up and do
stuff I guess they're having like stay
home and do nothing people are like yeah
no that's not gonna work for me right
there was it which is why I'm
theoretically going doing the live
videos because I I don't know what it
looks so like yet I'm just listening to
the call and we'll see you we'll see how
how it goes but that like how do we put
people to work in a way that that
actually is useful that's like there is
something coming down the pipeline we
can create it together so that there is
a space for everyone so that you can log
on and like I'm on Facebook so much
right now like just like like updating
the the stats on kovat like that's gonna
do something like it's like watching the
numbers increase like that's gonna spark
some kind of ingenuity or watching all
the news from around the world and I'm
like okay you actually this is not gonna
I'm not gonna come up with a solution to
cope in nineteen other people will and
and but like I don't know even even
though I know what I want to do with
this it's still I feel a little useless
because it's like well what's the step
right now to take what's the thing we
can do to like this oh that's the other
thing so I held the six the sixth
solution raising on labor and so now and
I did the notes for the first five and I
sell do the notes a sixth one and then I
want to hold the solution raising on the
solution raising for like here's what
we've done here's what we could do in
the future if we had you know infinite
money if we were if we were Facebook and
then what could we do with a hundred
thousand people it will actually be more
like how do we find ten thousand
$100,000 what can we actually create now
what's the to do adjacent possible to
actually do that maybe it's not to yet
to 10,000 it's to get to 100 and they
get to 1,000 and they got to to 10,000
but I think people even crowdfunding
campaigns right now like I feel like a
really basic crowdfunding campaign of
let's put people to work but first we
need the platform so we're gonna need to
put some tech people to work would done
in the right way would absolutely
generate a hundred thousand dollars and
ten thousand people and then you'd have
a smaller pool of um I tend ask people
were like yes put me somewhere a little
help you and it's like right but we
don't have it we don't have the platform
yet to do that so it's about you getting
to participate in watching that be
creative right or getting to do what we
wanted to do for projects right which is
like bring people on board and say what
you need from that which is what what
did come out of the labor project
raising was the adjacent possible of
creating a volunteer slash Skillshare
platform basically find out where you
can get paid and to find out where you
can use your your time for free so our
Facebook poster is Sam Turner hello Sam
pull it up and yeah the market aboard
and meaning deprived people it's about
two cars from that's like or is growing
mm-hmm as we speak I mean there's a lot
we do in society to not sit with our own
emotions and not spend time with the
people who we really wish we could spend
time with so busy I couldn't possibly
when I have time you have nothing but
time right now you're about to realize
that that's actually not but yeah I've
heard a number of like sort of you know
I guess like more successful like
well-off people who you know who have
been forced to stay at home and they're
like I kind of miss just hanging out
with my kids and like they're starting
to be like oh yeah
this is what I gave up for that oh yeah
like this is a part of the price that
I'm paying for whatever I'm doing and it
sounds like some of them were kind of
having contained a part of like maybe I
don't want to work that much because I
think you want to you know watch my kids
grow up and that kind of thing
and Sam's project is the it is for
civically minded people that are bored
and it's kind of game be project list
which fits oh cool you know some of the
other topics we've been floating around
so that was one of the two people who
filled out the project are you available
at 9:00 a.m. tomorrow Sam to come on the
meta project conversation or we're
bringing our projects to have any
conversation about what our projects
need and how we can facilitate with each
other it was just the two people who
filled out the doodle poll or a bit a
little tomorrow at 9 a.m. Pacific
Standard Time so you thought some
holding it this looks like one of the
first things I want whatever happens
with my live 6 o'clock show I'm like I
need a note-taker someone like not
because they're not gonna attend
everyone six days a week but having a
different person each day who is better
at that who can I thank you don't think
4 p.m. UTC because you you guys haven't
done like skip ahead yet right or your
spring forward then was usually eight
hours but I think it's seven right now
yeah they say if you go on Google and
put in 9:00 a.m. PST at all to not back
to your local time Sam is probably
better the most Ronnie guest cuz I think
it now is actually but I think they just
had to it okay yeah so I drove you I
don't think you ever said what what
you've been working on this last week
over Oh true so I have been working on
the specs for like the early early sore
a first coated version of wiki election
the goalless actually have somebody
coded while we're all stuck at home if
you're willing to at me I might send you
the specs just to see if that's
something that like is that detailed
enough for a developer or is that need
someone
and then I've been working a bit on sort
of the like planning for something like
together tech and it sounds like
something a bit like bored at home where
it's figuring out how can we actually
get projects listed what work needs to
be done and start trying to go make a
spot for people to actually come
together and start working on projects
and it's that than that just you know
try enough to go crazy stuck at home
which that's a fairly standard okay so
we have our meeting tomorrow and forgive
me jibley
what was the how did you phrase the
topic for that one because it was just
kind of how to work together with our
different projects or was it more
specific than that yeah I just have a
project meeting to had I don't remember
what exactly how I phrased the doodle
poll but it was like when he available
to get together and talk about our
projects and that was open and it was
very specific it was like this Friday
this Saturday this Sunday and this
Monday it wasn't like an ongoing one but
am i it's great that it's I was hoping
people would either be available right
now during this time period or the
Saturday one so we could just keep it if
we wanted to change that into a weekly
or bi-weekly thing so that people are
showing up sacred I think having that so
that it's every other week 9:00 a.m.
2:00 p.m. and having to be a project
meeting is one of the most powerful
things we can do so that people can show
up and facilitate and then as people
have a need for a specific project
raising right where they haven't asked
and they're trying to get over it we can
focus our time on um this will be
something we decide or not decide
tomorrow but focus our time on what's
pertinent right like I don't I don't I
can't think of an app we don't need
right now but there's certain ones where
it's like maybe not the biggest priority
as much as that's a priority for that
person right like something like we
collection and reasons score we really
do need sense-making right now like
that's what
this is showing us that we don't trust
our politicians in media and that's
costing all of us the poverty costs all
of us that a lack of health care like
all of these things were interconnected
and so any project that showcasing that
is yeah I don't I didn't answer the
question did I know you did all right
though I don't know how I ordered it but
that's like in my head we get together
for projects and figure it out as we go
yeah like what's gonna be the most
powerful use of our time just keep it
open-ended and Sam if we're on discord
or telegram right now everything's on
the Facebook group which is group slash
together tech now Oh actually boom calm
/kreut slash together tech yeah the
displays is game B projects is the name
yeah maybe project of yours if you're
searching for it and if you're not
searching for it yeah linked to from the
game me homepage and promptly from Kim B
well I guess game B ho pages links from
game P projects open to all projects not
just game view projects right anyone who
has a project that is game be like even
if they've never heard a game B yes
right I care less about you knowing how
to practice so make a role and more
about hey you maybe keep your ego
bidding check oh we have conversations
but even that if you ought to have a
huge ego and you're doing something big
awesome awesome just make it up
yeah that's the place the one you're
watching it on right now is the one yeah
that's right I forgot no Jubilee we
started in his post he was asking about
some things to be handy to know about
each project cuz I think he's asking for
feedback like project name project
summary general category so we did us
did we end up doing that spreadsheet
like that I don't know if we did it
exactly like that but yeah
would be and honestly it's probably
better do your own doodle poll that's in
this specific format you want it to be
air started judo pull like just pull
just a little we go it's not even a poll
what is it called they can form four I
think yeah we have it somewhere we could
send it we could send it to Sam if he's
interested I think that might be good
the one that cuz it looks pretty similar
to what we had I think we had about
fifteen or sixteen people fill fill it
out I don't think I filled it up for
project raising because we project crazy
didn't exist yet so yeah I wouldn't know
sorry solution raising not project
raising so really a problem like he was
calling drug thing yeah
yes he just mentioned they don't think
anyone responded Julie did a comment but
records and I didn't I think that was
probably because we asked that question
probably before you shortly before he
came in the group so people may have
already they may have already used up
people's goodwill to fill those out
myself but yeah if we can find that I
wonder if I have it anywhere we'll try
and get it to you and then yeah if he
could make that call we can discuss it
more on Saturday if you're available for
p.m. it is 4:00 p.m. GMT and are posted
in the Facebook group itself if we have
the same problem we had on one of the
project raisins for too many people
showed up oh well can rotate in and out
and we can yeah good problem to have
that we know to go to zoom the following
week or figure it out from there
I think Zoo does it do one of the big
tech companies own Zune already oh think
so but zoom has been getting in trouble
over the last couple of days because
people found out that even if you aren't
signed into Facebook on your phone it's
still sending information about the
meeting to Facebook so it's probably
some kind of a deal I don't think we
actually own it but I was like they're
about to become one of the tech giant's
because of everyone using them during
this period of time like it's like it
went from a somewhat obscure something
most of us had heard about of it not
everyone - like what's this zoom and how
does everyone use it and I've seen so
many things posted on Facebook of like
celebrities and stuff and everyone's
using a zoom broom pretty crazy how fast
they're gonna take off which doesn't if
you wonder if their service is gonna
start to suffer but but I guess if
they're on like yeah I mean their
servers are only so big right that if
the whole world's on them they can't
deal with all of that at once but how
fast can they upgrade to get yeah if
they're using cloud resources though
they might be able to just pay for it
it's been pretty resilient I've used it
on three different things this week and
haven't seen I see additional issues
which is surprising actually yes that's
one of the benefits of cloud computing
fine not to uh whoever I'm gonna guess
all of the Facebook user is Sam which is
a bad bad guess but the buy shares since
sue I'm not buying shares in anything I
don't know if money's coming back I
don't know I'm like this is the one that
possibly we don't come back from in the
best or worst way
like people are waking so it's like
where do I invest money nowhere because
it's tied to the dollar and or I've got
some cryptocurrency UVI stuffed you're
no different governments don't but
that's just my own apocalyptic thinking
of like that was before the pandemic as
well yeah other people who are still
speculating in the market go ahead buy
shares and zoom if that's something you
can do if it's a public company
we are not a public company but you can
buy shares in goodwill and just
participating if together tech just
showing up showing up let's let's let's
do it
that is like what I think my favorite
thing about this pandemic is what like a
troll alluded to that people are not
sitting at home bored they're sitting at
home overwhelmed and they don't know
what to do yeah and they don't know how
to connect to people and they don't but
like people who have any amount of like
right I'm anxious it's go out and help
someone and you realize that like that
is payments in and of itself it's like I
can't handle this what can I do oh I can
grocery shop for someone I can
coordinated a zoom meeting I can do an
online yoga class I can do and so many
people are doing them for free that it
becomes like well why would I pay for it
why would I you know like I love to pay
what you can because I'm people who have
jobs still and have accessory to income
jobs and household can pay more and
people who just lost those jobs that
have nothing and turn how they're gonna
pay rent or food can still get you know
yeah there's been some cool stuff I
think a couple of like animal shelters
ran out of animals to adopt because
there was this big call to like to
foster and they were like sorry we're
closed or all of our animals are gone
they're all being fostered right
we also some of a lot of our
distilleries this is probably happening
up in Canada too or converted over to
remember different graces in a few
months but yeah sure right yeah there
was there's one in Dallas called buzz
balls they were one of the first people
to put kind of the wine in the little
bitty cups with we could just take the
lid off they I think they patented that
technology that's now used all over the
place I think they were the one maybe
not actually I'm wrong there's another
company but anyways there was a story in
the papers them and a couple of our
other breweries are now creating hand
sanitizer cool your chairs again people
I don't I actually don't think the
reason we're out of it in this store and
people are stocking up to sell it but
that's a little tiny piece of it most
people just want to know they have
enough on hand but but over producing it
means that you bring down the
cost for everyone which means if you
need it you can have it and if you were
stockpiling those are the ones we heard
and that's where like for the last few
years of like cooperation outcompetes
competition and this is what I mean in
the marketplace when you're willing to
give your services away for free people
can't start them when you're willing to
like create the thing that we really
have need make the supply meet the
demand instead of pricing it at supply
meets demands then you hurt the bad
players and not the good players and the
more like this is happening again and
again of people like Mike I can only
imagine if we had the ability to
actually focus people in like if right
now we had 20 people working on each of
the solution raisins or sorry each of
the yes which Amazings that would be
amazing like I I just made a list of the
six thing that we did right like if we
had the food app that we talked about
and the education app that was like more
not about replacing or current education
system but right now looking like maybe
but we do want it to replace our current
education system and so like food
education transportation labor
infectious disease and community and if
we were able to do anything in any of
those places and everyone knew they
didn't need a tech degree that can be as
technologically inept as I am he's show
up and still have like right this is
what I wanted to do though right this is
what I would love out of a food app this
is what the more were able to for me
anyway like focus on the solution Tracy
but then actually raise them actually
like how do we get 10,000 people and
$100,000 it's not that hard it's hard
for me but not for 40 of us not 400 of
us to figure out how to get 10 people
each and then 10 people each and then
were there we can use exponential
growth in a whole positive way that's
not a haha stay at home with the
pandemic it's like see how this keeps EE
well people's laugh lack of math skills
though is gonna kill us like I don't
think I realized how much people lacked
basic math skills it's like that's
person dot that's percent not
percentages reading two talking
percentages this is brand new that's not
the same we don't wait till this gets to
the flu to start acting but but that
like like people are not acting the way
we want them to act and the current game
a solution is to impose new laws and
fines and get the military on the street
and do and I don't know anything else to
do right now that would have any kind of
an effect but you have to deal with
people where they are and it's like why
are people still them in the streets
they don't understand they don't trust
the information that's given they don't
feel connected to their neighbors so
they're not going to look out for them
they're not gonna they don't feel like
they're gonna get looked out after and
they're terrified of the economic impact
health impact everything has they just
have blinders on it's like it we could
later on I mean like if reason score and
wiki election were already in existence
we'd have somewhat the information thing
covered right of like where do we go for
information that we can trust because
we've said we can trust it if we had a
connection app that wasn't Facebook and
was actually like you can go talk about
anything right our zooms scheduler
meeting thing we talked about a lot then
and an easy way to find community either
physical like I wouldn't go to the city
right now is really scary well we don't
have a place for you but maybe in six
months to a year if you work with this
group of people and like there are ways
that we can meet people where they are
we would have a bigger impact then like
stay inside because you're you're stupid
if you don't when they feel that like no
you're stupid for staying inside my
business is going under you don't
understand that this is not a thing I'm
just like well no virus is our thing and
they don't listen to logic
they're math they're master then it's
like people are like this is the enemy
I'm like it's not even an enemy because
it's not it's not doing it on purpose
and it's not gonna listen to reason or
borders or how you want the economy to
run it's just it's not
the force of nature it just is it's not
right or wrong it's just it's the
weather
yeah and it's actually someone on the
Omega call was talking about and I'm
gonna butcher it because it's already
two degrees of separation but how this
virus itself I mean all viruses hijack
your system to make copies of it for you
but for you alright to make copies of
itself with you or your factory in your
bodies yourselves but this one actually
trains your body to attack it basically
is an autoimmune disease like it trains
you to attack itself and the way that I
was no no it was David who described it
and was like oh this is like human
humanity right now like this this virus
is capitalism like it is the like or
like the bad side of it the the were
just focused on this one thing and then
it's also like diminishing returns right
now we're seeing how we focus not only
one thing it causes havoc in every other
space but this has to be have to focus
on this one biological thing at the same
time and showcasing all of the cracks
from us only focusing on profit from
like profit being our only factor in
every single and industry so everything
is so close to like the profit margin
and everything is so that things that
fall apart instead of us figuring out
how do we how do we create supply that
meets demand how do we have ingenuity
where you don't need to get paid because
now yeah I mean people understandably
want to get paid but at the same time
like well if I'm not getting paid just
put me to use and it's like if we
actually had enough of those people we
would nobody would ever have to go back
to work like we could actually focus
energy on are we fixing the problem and
do we have at the resort do we have our
needs met do we have food do we have
clothing do we have shelter and then
whatever monetary / job system wants to
be made on top of that great people
aren't as desperate you're gonna have to
pay them all I'm gonna have to it that
was me talking for a while
yeah yeah I don't have any other
specific topics I might have to leave a
little early all right that's fine it's
9:00 a.m. it's one of the for my six my
live show I'm gonna be doing I'm sure
I'm gonna have to try and find a co-host
either like one either oddball people
looking for oddball co-hosts meaning
they come one time or like someone
co-host with me every Monday and someone
every Tuesday and someone every I'll
just work better to have but instead of
this or we're kind of talking to each
other and maybe paying attention to the
comments it is about paying attention to
the comments it is about like try not oh
how do we how do it how do we do that
because I'm not it and even when I'm
live by myself and it's even more
awkward it's like wait I have to read it
makes sense and I don't have someone
else to run it by on video but I'm gonna
figure it out that's it saying like the
oddball say it might seem a saying I
think it's from dr. Seuss saying you
have to be odd to be number one all
right guys all right see you tomorrow
all right it's like weird suggest
pausing doesn't really quite work well
what is your what is your thing that if
you had it solved right now wiki
election could be up and running in who
really ended up idea why the election we
really need to see Trump's all of our
politicians incompetence just how did
different politicians and Ansel cope in
nineteen but yeah I mean like there's a
bunch of steps the next one I think is
to actually get a prototype up because
it's just really hard like people like
the idea but it's it's nebulous like
that that sounds great yeah flying car
sounds great tell me when you have it
right and I think it's kind of in that
state now so that's why now I'm trying
to focus on getting that prototype so
that I can actually show it and I think
the current plan is to do the thing that
I've been talking about for a while
where it's like there's sort of two
different versions of it one is for
protection of people that like
everything is available to the public
and it sort of
like a sandbox and then there's gonna be
the actual politician version where at
least to start what that's gonna be like
some of it might be visible but most of
it's gonna be for members only while
we're still working Kings oh it's for
the most part I have no plans to get
involved in the u.s. election the way
that it seems like it's going I don't
think like I don't want my fingerprints
anywhere close to that because I don't
think it's going to end up being good so
no but isn't there also like if wiki
election was there you might have a
different outcome than if if it was
there a year ago yes I think it's just
it's to like to show up in the last like
two three months and just like I
wouldn't want to swing it in any
direction because I don't like where
it's headed right now I don't want my
name or wiki election anywhere close to
it but yeah ideally we're available like
at the start of the primaries I think it
you know it could have made a difference
if it had users but that's long since
sailed so fair enough well it's not
what's gonna say my collection no it's
gone it's all good and it's oh that's
how it's gonna say that reminds me you
have to reminding me of it so just like
I'm going out I'm not going off of pot
right now but I'm trying not to smoke it
until 6:00 p.m. for those of you don't
smoke pot that seems like a ridiculous
it's like home alone all day but I don't
have to drive anywhere I don't think Oh
anywhere usually I'd be like 10 yeah
like maybe smoke a little bit but well
the rest of the world has my full
permission to sit around and smoke pot
for the next few weeks I it's just like
the two times in my life I went off the
more than two times but two times my
life or it made no sense to go off at
that but I'm like no I really do need to
is what I went through radiation what
doctors are like this is the time it's
the restart and then during the pandemic
for like everyone else is sitting around
sleep on them like I want to focus and
so part of what when I go live at six
forty at night I'm gonna smoke pot right
beforehand and be like yeah this is me
hi online totally yeah during the night
I interested in like being one of the
guests like on a certain day
the Monday guests or something like that
well Friday's is not I'm normally not
going to have them on Fridays but she's
been so ironic also that tonight's the
first night I'm gonna host it and then
because I want to go live for a week
straight and then I'm not gonna do the
one Friday night it's just so I have one
night I know that he isn't there and
then cohousing has their courtyard song
at 6:45 so I was like till 6:40 cuz that
seems like and then bedtime and have
been having that go and I'm trying to
have what I had already in place before
the pandemic the idea cafes and make a
group and this in the Saturday and then
the live videos and whatever video want
to put out on Monday Wednesday and
Friday and then not be online other than
that like not sit there watch him a
numbers go out but we'll see that's the
whole other level
what's up being such a grab there's
nothing in that we eat them in the plane
we had three one of them dropped in the
plane and we didn't eat in them we each
ate one so our ears would pop but I saw
gum in your room on your floor you go
eat that why you need gum I don't know
well this is only day one really oh yeah
sure
although I mean can't really call it a
vacation if you're just quarantine to
somewhere else no you cannot it was
nothing not the best and I you know any
of our stuff wait for that oh this is
harder to do though like you can have it
go on without you when it's only two
people I hope not
she dropped it's like my screen cracked
she can actually like turn it on oh no
it's 50/50 we'll see we'll see how that
well luckily it's not the iPad it's just
over $100 tablet it a Facebook Messenger
has a kids version but it's the most
unlike this is not easy to use Facebook
it's like I added people that won't let
myriad their kids be I don't even know
it's ridiculous I'm like Facebook I
expect better
from you you have all the money and all
the people think you have to go trying
to build anything for kids right now is
ridiculous is there's so many rules and
like the price it makes sense like I'll
I have to request permission for her to
connect with them through their parents
but I'm friends with all their parents
on Facebook so I added them to one of
the apps now they don't exist now it's
like I can't survive like no and so 8025
search for the name write search for Tom
which is her friend right and then I'll
be like oh it's so the requests to get
sent to me so I have to figure out who
tom is right well how it's like is it a
kid or is it data then it's like and
then he doesn't matter cuz they're not
they're like what
so is so I went from the primary boobs
basically the mom the mom being my
contact to trying to find the dad cuz
the dad was like let's go through the
other person can I request your kids
edition but no because it was just one
parent in any way whatever it's a little
bit ridiculous but they're having a lot
of fun calling back and forth in to some
degree because the closing kids off to
stay in their apartment which is hard
they can't be in and out of each other's
places they're like on messenger and she
can participate in that in a way that
she couldn't participate be basically
they're right like I'm like oh I don't
and like their communities designed to
be with each other right and now they
can't like it's like and so they have
smaller houses and they don't like I'm
like how do you stay inside with that
many kids without many the person the
the neighbor that I got in conflict with
right know has two adults actually he
might be he's a lawyer so he might be an
essential service is still working but I
don't know it depends if you they have
cases open and if that's not me I don't
know but she's at home with the two kids
for sure and the dog and Minh if they
were someone who could leaves her in her
downtime now it's not working anymore
like okay well this is gonna get its
gonna get fun everywhere like oh the
over height means of emotions and people
you know even me here I'm like oh the
upstairs neighbors are here more often
and dad's here more often
i silver lining and pandemics I have two
possible construction sites one next
door that they haven't put up fencing
but the people have moved out and then
the two doors down the other way that
has a fence all the way around and I'm
like oh I don't think they're gonna
start now that one started it's gonna be
probably until this is done
no I think instruction was made an
essential service but it's also not an
essential service especially if the
house is already there yeah like it's
different if it was torn down in your
part way through building it but it's
like this is not quite not quite thing
okay she was say goodbye to YouTube so
that all right bye YouTube back Facebook
we'll see you tomorrow at 9 a.m. for our
project meeting Pacific Standard Time is
the time and hopefully we'll see see
who's there it's really clear